kingdomofpets.com 2019-03-11

# Kingdom of Pets Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy:

#### General

Your use of this website is governed by our Terms of Use. Accordingly, this Privacy Policy must be read in conjunction with our Terms of Use.

#### Information Collection and Use

KINGDOM OF PETS Ltd. is the sole owner of any information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. KINGDOM OF PETS Ltd. collects information from our users at several different points on our website. We stress that all personal information is always treated as personal and confidential, unless specifically stated otherwise.

An example of this is that when you sign up to a KINGDOM OF PETS newsletter series (6 Day Courses or free trials) your email address is only recorded so that we can send you KINGDOM OF PETS newsletters and/or free trial.

#### Correction/Updating Personal Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove the personal data you provided to us. This can be done by clicking the “change subscription options” link at the bottom of any email from us or by sending us an email.

#### Success Stories and Reviews

We only use names, photos and testimonials or reviews of people who have given us permission to do so. If you have feedback about any KINGDOM OF PETS product then please email us. Please state whether or not we are allowed to use your feedback as a testimonial.

#### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

#### Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that KINGDOM OF PETS Ltd. is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website.

#### Security

This website takes certain precautions to protect our users’ information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. However, there is unfortunately no way yet for the industry to guarantee that the information you transmit through the Internet is entirely secure.

#### Notice to Parents

This website is not specifically directed at or intended for children. Our public forums, such as the chat rooms and message boards, are considered non-confidential communications. Much of the content in these public areas, including the content within specific messages, comments or postings is provided by and is the responsibility of the third party creator of the communication or the person posting the information. KINGDOM OF PETS Ltd. does not control or endorse the content, messages or information found in any public forum and, therefore, KINGDOM OF PETS Ltd. specifically disclaims any liability with regard to public forums and any actions resulting from a user’s participation in any public forum. KINGDOM OF PETS Ltd. has no responsibility for such content and is merely providing access to such content as a service to its users.

The best way for you as a parent to protect your child’s online privacy and safety is through supervision and parental guidance. Visit the sites that your child uses. Good communication with the child will help him/her be more aware of the risks involved in providing strangers with personal information, especially when using chat-rooms or e-mail. We strongly recommend that you supervise your children’s activities when using these services as you would in any public area.

For your information, as a parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 years old, you have the right to review your child’s personal information gathered by Internet sites. You may ask to have your child’s information deleted from their records and refuse to allow any further collection or use of your child’s information. KINGDOM OF PETS Ltd. does not collect information from registrants who indicate to be under 13 years old.

#### Notification of Changes

If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes via the Privacy Policy links on the website so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

Thank you for visiting this KINGDOM OF PETS Ltd. website.
